inter-lumi.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Privacy Statement**  
America Expo Group takes the privacy of its users seriously. This Privacy Policy explains our practices in relation to the use of your personal information that you may provide to America Expo Group through the use of any of our services on the site. Our goal is to make it possible for you to be certain of responsible and confidential treatment of your data.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
Personal information collected from customers through various methods of communications with America Expo Group will be stored and managed for America Expo Group's internal use. Personal data includes, but is not limited to, name, address, company name, company address, phone number, fax number, email address, as well as questions answered on survey or registration forms. Personal information may be, with the consent of America Expo Group, shared with other organizations or America Expo Group's customers for the purpose of facilitating business relationships in our customer's best interests.

**Security**  
This site utilizes a secure server to protect your financial and professional information. Secure server software is used to encrypt the information sent between your internet browser and our internet site. This ensures the security of your professional and financial transaction details when using this site. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information you have given to us and may, on occasion, request proof of identity before we disclose any personal information to you.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are commonly used to facilitate transmission and to provide more useful features. We use these devices to find out more about the use of our websites and user preferences, in order to improve our services. Cookies are nothing more than a simple text file. They are not executable programs, and consequently it is impossible for a cookie to contain a virus, or any other application. Cookies are also very small, and you run no risk of filling your hard drive with too many cookies. You may set your browser to reject cookies, or tell you when a cookie is being sent. Cookies are necessary for some features of the website to work, e.g., to maintain continuity during a session. If they are not accepted, those features may not work properly.

**Disclosure of Information**  
It is not our aim to use or pass on personal data without the data subject permission and for purposes other than those stated at the time the data was collected. We will keep the personal data we hold confidential but may provide information to: 

  * Group companies
  * Responsible sales and service partners
  * Trade fair and exhibition industry associations
  * Those responsible for processing order data 
  * Exhibitors - always in order to fulfil the purposes of facilitating business relationships
  * Public bodies, but only when legally obligated to do so

**Right of Objection**  
Apart from the mandatory data storage for the purposes of conducting business, you have the right to demand at any time that your data not be retained for other purposes. If you want your personal data to be blocked, please contact us via e-mail: info@america-expo.com.

In addition, we offer you the possibility of correcting or altering the data collected during registration.

**Disclaimer**  
This site contains links to external sites. America Expo Group is not responsible for, and has no control over, the content of such sites. Information on this site, or available via hypertext link from this site, is made available without responsibility on the part of America Expo Group.

America Expo Group disclaims all responsibility and liability (including negligence) in relation to information on or accessible from this site.
